download the prudential uganda app from
either play store or ios if you are a
new user click on sign up to create an
account fill in your phone number
excluding the first zero the same phone
number that you provided to prudential
in the proposal form it should also be
the only number you use to access all
your policy statements and receipts in
case you have more than one policy use
your registered phone number always
exclude the first xero or registered
email address and password to login to
your profile by clicking on login an otp
code will be sent to your phone as an
sms or on your registered email address
once you receive the otp code update it
and click on verify upon correct
authentication you will land on the my
dashboard page download the statement to
review premium statement click on my
policies to view your policy details
back on the dashboard click on payment
platforms to pay using either mobile
money or visa card also by clicking on
receipts you will be able to review your
transaction history for